Okay, I'm going to try to address this as simplistically as possible. I see people come
in my comments and they say things like, we shouldn't be talking about Palestine, we should
be talking about the Congo. And I think that for some of those people, they think that by saying
this, they are showing an allegiance to quote unquote their people. They think that they are
somehow, you know, calling people out who they feel are putting their attention in the wrong places.
What I want to bring attention to is how this is such a myopic reductive view of what global
imperialism really is. And I know that some people actually don't give a damn at all. So they're not
going to be listening to what I have to say anyway, because they really are just agent provocateurs
who just want to feel like they're doing something. They're contrarians who really just want to feel
like they're undermining folks because they have their own insecurity. So if you're one of those
people, just know that this isn't for you. But if you genuinely, if you're genuinely about
humanitarian efforts and about the undermining of the empire, it starts with education. You have
to understand that much of the conflict in the Congo is largely in part because Israel is utilizing
the minerals of the Congo. They are the ones in there. They're the ones who got the diamonds, who
got the cobalt, who are actually using these things to fund their own empires. And they are using these
things to fund the weaponry that they are using on Palestinians and that they are testing on
Palestinians so that they can come and test it on Americans. When they come and test it on Americans, do
you think that it's going to be about white Americans? I mean, I'm just, I'm curious because as we're
watching these universities be cracked down upon with riot police, you're seeing middle-aged white
professors being pushed to the ground for defending their students' right to protest, which is literally
the First Amendment right. You're seeing cop cities, which are militarized training camps for police
forces built all over this nation. Who do you think those are going to be used to suppress?
So when we look at these things and we add them up, we say, okay, so in our current very urgent fight
against Israel, Zionism, and Palestinians, which by the way, is also being challenged by legislation.
So it's not just militarized police. It's not just like extreme people. No, there is actually
legislation in America that is working to be passed to say that challenging or speaking ill of Israel,
a whole other country, is going to be considered illegal. So now if you're fighting for the Congo
and Israel is the one that is very, very involved in doing harm in the Congo, and they say that talking
bad about Israel is a crime. Do you think that helps us fight for the Congo? I didn't think so
because it doesn't. There are donations to be made to the Congo. There's education that needs to be had
about the Congo. There is absolutely a heightened level of communication that needs to be had about
the Congo because a lot of people really don't understand what's going on or actual initiatives
to take. But coming in comments where people are speaking loudly about the carnage that is happening
in Gaza right now, in Israel right now, does not help the Congo. Because along with speaking about
what is happening on the ground, people are also speaking about how Israel is using this Palestine
conflict to bone up its strength to be able to do this wherever it wants to. So in challenging them
doing that in Palestine, we are effectively or at least essentially challenging them being able to
continue to do this in the Congo. There are resources here in the captions that can help you get more
informed about the Congo and that also can help you to inform more people about the Congo instead of
thinking that undermining people informing about Palestine is somehow helpful to the people in the
Congo because I can promise you they don't think it is.